WJZ-TV Collection R0129.WJZ R0129.WJZ
Stage
- Evening Magazine, 1977-1991; EVMAG; 8 Reels 2 inch videotape: Quad; 4,676 Cassettes
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-21; WJZ-EVMAG-121-009 (Mixed materials 121, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-21; WJZ-EVMAG-121-010 (Mixed materials 121, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-21; WJZ-EVMAG-121-011 (Mixed materials 121, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-121-012 (Mixed materials 121, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-121-013 (Mixed materials 121, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-121-014 (Mixed materials 121, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-121-015 (Mixed materials 121, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-121-016 (Mixed materials 121, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-25; WJZ-EVMAG-122-001 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-26; WJZ-EVMAG-122-002 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-26; WJZ-EVMAG-122-003 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-27; WJZ-EVMAG-122-004 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-11-27-1986-11-28; WJZ-EVMAG-122-005 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-01-1986-12-02; WJZ-EVMAG-122-006 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-03-1986-12-04; WJZ-EVMAG-122-007 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-05-1986-12-08; WJZ-EVMAG-122-008 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-06; WJZ-EVMAG-122-009 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-06; WJZ-EVMAG-122-010 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-06; WJZ-EVMAG-122-011 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-09-1986-12-10; WJZ-EVMAG-122-012 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-11-1986-12-12; WJZ-EVMAG-122-013 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-15-1986-12-16; WJZ-EVMAG-122-014 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-17-1986-12-18; WJZ-EVMAG-122-015 (Mixed materials 122, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-19-1986-12-22; WJZ-EVMAG-123-001 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-23-1986-12-24; WJZ-EVMAG-123-002 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-25-1986-12-26; WJZ-EVMAG-123-003 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-29-1986-12-30; WJZ-EVMAG-123-004 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1986-12-31-1987-01-01; WJZ-EVMAG-123-005 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987; WJZ-EVMAG-123-006 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987; WJZ-EVMAG-123-007 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-02-1987-01-05; WJZ-EVMAG-123-008 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-02; WJZ-EVMAG-123-009 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-02; WJZ-EVMAG-123-010 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-02; WJZ-EVMAG-123-011 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-06-1987-01-07; WJZ-EVMAG-123-012 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-06-1987-01-07; WJZ-EVMAG-123-013 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-08-1987-01-09; WJZ-EVMAG-123-014 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-09; WJZ-EVMAG-123-015 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-12-1987-01-13; WJZ-EVMAG-123-016 (Mixed materials 123, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-12-1987-01-15; WJZ-EVMAG-124-001 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-16-1987-01-19; WJZ-EVMAG-124-002 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-18; WJZ-EVMAG-124-003 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-19-1987-01-21; WJZ-EVMAG-124-004 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-20-1987-01-21; WJZ-EVMAG-124-005 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-22-1987-01-23; WJZ-EVMAG-124-006 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-24; WJZ-EVMAG-124-007 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-24; WJZ-EVMAG-124-008 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-24; WJZ-EVMAG-124-009 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-24; WJZ-EVMAG-124-010 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-26-1987-01-27; WJZ-EVMAG-124-011 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-27; WJZ-EVMAG-124-012 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-27-1987-01-28; WJZ-EVMAG-124-013 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-26-1987-01-28; WJZ-EVMAG-124-014 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-29; WJZ-EVMAG-124-015 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-30-1987-02-02; WJZ-EVMAG-124-016 (Mixed materials 124, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-01-27; WJZ-EVMAG-125-001 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02; WJZ-EVMAG-125-002 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-03-1987-02-04; WJZ-EVMAG-125-003 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-03-1987-02-04; WJZ-EVMAG-125-004 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-05; WJZ-EVMAG-125-005 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-05-1987-02-06; WJZ-EVMAG-125-006 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-07; WJZ-EVMAG-125-007 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-07; WJZ-EVMAG-125-008 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-07; WJZ-EVMAG-125-009 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-09-1987-02-10; WJZ-EVMAG-125-010 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-09-1987-02-12; WJZ-EVMAG-125-011 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-11-1987-02-12; WJZ-EVMAG-125-012 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-13-1987-02-16; WJZ-EVMAG-125-013 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-16-1987-02-17; WJZ-EVMAG-125-014 (Mixed materials 125, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-17; WJZ-EVMAG-126-001 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-17; WJZ-EVMAG-126-002 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-17-1987-02-18; WJZ-EVMAG-126-003 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-19-1987-02-20; WJZ-EVMAG-126-004 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-25; WJZ-EVMAG-126-005 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-27; WJZ-EVMAG-126-006 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-02-27-1987-03-02; WJZ-EVMAG-126-007 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-02-1987-03-06; WJZ-EVMAG-126-008 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-03-1987-03-04; WJZ-EVMAG-126-009 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-05; WJZ-EVMAG-126-010 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-05-1987-03-06; WJZ-EVMAG-126-011 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-09-1987-03-10; WJZ-EVMAG-126-012 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-11; WJZ-EVMAG-126-013 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-11-1987-03-13; WJZ-EVMAG-126-014 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-13-1987-03-16; WJZ-EVMAG-126-015 (Mixed materials 126, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-16; WJZ-EVMAG-127-001 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-17-1987-03-18; WJZ-EVMAG-127-002 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-19-1987-03-20; WJZ-EVMAG-127-003 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-23; WJZ-EVMAG-127-004 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-23-1987-03-24; WJZ-EVMAG-127-005 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-25-1987-03-26; WJZ-EVMAG-127-006 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-27-1987-03-31; WJZ-EVMAG-127-007 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-03-31-1987-04-03; WJZ-EVMAG-127-008 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04; WJZ-EVMAG-127-009 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04; WJZ-EVMAG-127-010 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-01-1987-04-02; WJZ-EVMAG-127-011 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-03-1987-04-06; WJZ-EVMAG-127-012 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-07-1987-04-08; WJZ-EVMAG-127-013 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-07-1987-04-08; WJZ-EVMAG-127-014 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-09-1987-04-10; WJZ-EVMAG-127-015 (Mixed materials 127, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-13-1987-04-14; WJZ-EVMAG-128-001 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-13-1987-04-17; WJZ-EVMAG-128-002 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-15-1987-04-16; WJZ-EVMAG-128-003 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-17-1987-04-20; WJZ-EVMAG-128-004 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-20; WJZ-EVMAG-128-005 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-21; WJZ-EVMAG-128-006 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-23-1987-04-24; WJZ-EVMAG-128-007 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-25; WJZ-EVMAG-128-008 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-27-1987-04-28; WJZ-EVMAG-128-009 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-29; WJZ-EVMAG-128-010 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-04-29-1987-04-30; WJZ-EVMAG-128-011 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-04; WJZ-EVMAG-128-012 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-07-1987-05-08; WJZ-EVMAG-128-013 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-11-1987-05-12; WJZ-EVMAG-128-014 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-12-1987-05-15; WJZ-EVMAG-128-015 (Mixed materials 128, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-13-1987-05-14; WJZ-EVMAG-129-001 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-15-1987-05-18; WJZ-EVMAG-129-002 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-18; WJZ-EVMAG-129-003 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-18-1987-05-21; WJZ-EVMAG-129-004 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-19; WJZ-EVMAG-129-005 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-19-1987-05-20; WJZ-EVMAG-129-006 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-21-1987-05-22; WJZ-EVMAG-129-007 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-25-1987-05-26; WJZ-EVMAG-129-008 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-26; WJZ-EVMAG-129-009 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-26; WJZ-EVMAG-129-010 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-27-1987-05-28; WJZ-EVMAG-129-011 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-05-29-1987-06-01; WJZ-EVMAG-129-012 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-02-1987-06-03; WJZ-EVMAG-129-013 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-03; WJZ-EVMAG-129-014 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-04-1987-06-05; WJZ-EVMAG-129-015 (Mixed materials 129, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-05; WJZ-EVMAG-130-001 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06; WJZ-EVMAG-130-002 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-08; WJZ-EVMAG-130-003 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-08-1987-06-09; WJZ-EVMAG-130-004 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-09; WJZ-EVMAG-130-005 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-10; WJZ-EVMAG-130-006 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-10; WJZ-EVMAG-130-007 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-11-1987-06-12; WJZ-EVMAG-130-008 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-15-1987-06-19; WJZ-EVMAG-130-009 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-15-1987-06-16; WJZ-EVMAG-130-010 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-16-1987-06-30; WJZ-EVMAG-130-011 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-17; WJZ-EVMAG-130-012 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-17-1987-06-18; WJZ-EVMAG-130-013 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-19-1987-06-22; WJZ-EVMAG-130-014 (Mixed materials 130, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-25-1987-07-02; WJZ-EVMAG-131-001 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-25-1987-06-26; WJZ-EVMAG-131-002 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-29; WJZ-EVMAG-131-003 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-29; WJZ-EVMAG-131-004 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-29-1987-06-30; WJZ-EVMAG-131-005 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-30; WJZ-EVMAG-131-006 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-06-30; WJZ-EVMAG-131-007 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-01; WJZ-EVMAG-131-008 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-01-1987-07-02; WJZ-EVMAG-131-009 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-03-1987-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-131-010 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-07-1987-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-131-011 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-07-1987-07-14; WJZ-EVMAG-131-012 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-07-1987-07-08; WJZ-EVMAG-131-013 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-09; WJZ-EVMAG-131-014 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-09-1987-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-131-015 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-13-1987-07-14; WJZ-EVMAG-131-016 (Mixed materials 131, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-13-1987-07-15; WJZ-EVMAG-132-001 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-15; WJZ-EVMAG-132-002 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-15-1987-07-16; WJZ-EVMAG-132-003 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-17; WJZ-EVMAG-132-004 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-17-1987-07-20; WJZ-EVMAG-132-005 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-20-1987-07-22; WJZ-EVMAG-132-006 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-21-1987-07-22; WJZ-EVMAG-132-007 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-23-1987-07-24; WJZ-EVMAG-132-008 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-27-1987-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-132-009 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-27-1987-07-28; WJZ-EVMAG-132-010 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-29-1987-07-30; WJZ-EVMAG-132-011 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-07-31-1987-08-03; WJZ-EVMAG-132-012 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-03; WJZ-EVMAG-132-013 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-04-1987-08-05; WJZ-EVMAG-132-014 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-06-1987-08-07; WJZ-EVMAG-132-015 (Mixed materials 132, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-10-1987-08-11; WJZ-EVMAG-133-001 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-12; WJZ-EVMAG-133-002 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-12-1987-08-13; WJZ-EVMAG-133-003 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-14-1987-08-17; WJZ-EVMAG-133-004 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-18-1987-08-19; WJZ-EVMAG-133-005 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-20-1987-08-21; WJZ-EVMAG-133-006 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-24-1987-08-25; WJZ-EVMAG-133-007 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-25; WJZ-EVMAG-133-008 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-26-1987-08-27; WJZ-EVMAG-133-009 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-28; WJZ-EVMAG-133-010 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-28-1987-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-133-011 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-08-31-1987-09-04; WJZ-EVMAG-133-012 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-01-1987-09-02; WJZ-EVMAG-133-013 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-03-1987-09-04; WJZ-EVMAG-133-014 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-07-1987-09-08; WJZ-EVMAG-133-015 (Mixed materials 133, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-07-1987-09-11; WJZ-EVMAG-134-001 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-09-1987-09-10; WJZ-EVMAG-134-002 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-10; WJZ-EVMAG-134-003 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-11; WJZ-EVMAG-134-004 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-11-1987-09-14; WJZ-EVMAG-134-005 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-14-1987-09-16; WJZ-EVMAG-134-006 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-16-1987-09-17; WJZ-EVMAG-134-007 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-17; WJZ-EVMAG-134-008 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-18-1987-09-21; WJZ-EVMAG-134-009 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-22-1987-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-134-010 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-22-1987-09-23; WJZ-EVMAG-134-011 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-24-1987-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-134-012 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-28-1987-09-29; WJZ-EVMAG-134-013 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-29; WJZ-EVMAG-134-014 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-09-30-1987-10-01; WJZ-EVMAG-134-015 (Mixed materials 134, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10; WJZ-EVMAG-135-001 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10; WJZ-EVMAG-135-002 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10; WJZ-EVMAG-135-003 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10; WJZ-EVMAG-135-004 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-06-1987-10-07; WJZ-EVMAG-135-005 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-08-1987-10-09; WJZ-EVMAG-135-006 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-12-1987-10-13; WJZ-EVMAG-135-007 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-14; WJZ-EVMAG-135-008 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-14-1987-10-15; WJZ-EVMAG-135-009 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-16; WJZ-EVMAG-135-010 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-16-1987-10-19; WJZ-EVMAG-135-011 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-20-1987-10-21; WJZ-EVMAG-135-012 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-20-1987-10-21; WJZ-EVMAG-135-013 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-22; WJZ-EVMAG-135-014 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-22-1987-10-23; WJZ-EVMAG-135-015 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-23; WJZ-EVMAG-135-016 (Mixed materials 135, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-27; WJZ-EVMAG-136-001 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-26; WJZ-EVMAG-136-002 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-26; WJZ-EVMAG-136-003 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-26-1987-10-27; WJZ-EVMAG-136-004 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-27-1987-10-30; WJZ-EVMAG-136-005 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-28-1987-10-29; WJZ-EVMAG-136-006 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-10-30-1987-11-02; WJZ-EVMAG-136-007 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11; WJZ-EVMAG-136-008 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-03-1987-11-04; WJZ-EVMAG-136-009 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-03; WJZ-EVMAG-136-010 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-05-1987-11-06; WJZ-EVMAG-136-011 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-09; WJZ-EVMAG-136-012 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-09-1987-11-10; WJZ-EVMAG-136-013 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-10; WJZ-EVMAG-136-014 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-11; WJZ-EVMAG-136-015 (Mixed materials 136, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-11-1987-11-12; WJZ-EVMAG-137-001 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-13-1987-11-16; WJZ-EVMAG-137-002 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-17-1987-11-18; WJZ-EVMAG-137-003 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-18; WJZ-EVMAG-137-004 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-19-1987-11-20; WJZ-EVMAG-137-005 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-23-1987-11-24; WJZ-EVMAG-137-006 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-25-1987-11-26; WJZ-EVMAG-137-007 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-11-27-1987-11-30; WJZ-EVMAG-137-008 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12; WJZ-EVMAG-137-009 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-01; WJZ-EVMAG-137-010 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-01-1987-12-04; WJZ-EVMAG-137-011 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-07-1987-12-11; WJZ-EVMAG-137-012 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-02; WJZ-EVMAG-137-013 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-02-1987-12-03; WJZ-EVMAG-137-014 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-04-1987-12-07; WJZ-EVMAG-137-015 (Mixed materials 137, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-10-1987-12-11; WJZ-EVMAG-138-001 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-08-1987-12-09; WJZ-EVMAG-138-002 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-18-1987-12-21; WJZ-EVMAG-138-003 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-21-1987-12-24; WJZ-EVMAG-138-004 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-22-1987-12-23; WJZ-EVMAG-138-005 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-24-1987-12-25; WJZ-EVMAG-138-006 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-28-1987-12-29; WJZ-EVMAG-138-007 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-30-1987-12-31; WJZ-EVMAG-138-008 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1987-12-31; WJZ-EVMAG-138-009 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988; WJZ-EVMAG-138-010 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-01-01-1988-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-138-011 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-01-06-1988-01-08; WJZ-EVMAG-138-012 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-01-05-1988-01-06; WJZ-EVMAG-138-013 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-01-06; WJZ-EVMAG-138-014 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-01-07-1988-01-08; WJZ-EVMAG-138-015 (Mixed materials 138, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-01-11-1988-01-13; WJZ-EVMAG-139-001 (Mixed materials 139, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-01-11-1988-01-12; WJZ-EVMAG-139-002 (Mixed materials 139, Tape 2)